<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Improv Festivals</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <updated>2024-02-05T00:01:29+00:00</updated>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <uri></uri>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 

 <entry>
   <title>IFO Impro Fest</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_24</id>
   <updated>2024-10-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The IFO Impro Fest ist one of Germany´s biggest international festival with workshop, shows, party and a lot of improv fun!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Das Improv Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Das_Improv_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Das_Improv_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-10-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Berlin’s long-form improv festival! Featuring the best alternative improv from across Europe and North America, with an exciting slate of headline acts from around the world and top-notch workshops and intensives, plus all the best improv Berlin itself has to offer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sign up for our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dasimprovfestival.com/newsletter/&quot;&gt;mailing list&lt;/a&gt; to get...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Improfestival Karlsruhe</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_24</id>
   <updated>2024-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a smashing success in the last few years we are happy to be back in 2024 with even more shows and workshops.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This year we have a selection of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;12 ensemble-members (10 actors, 1 musician and 1 technician)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;A total of 9 days workshops, including one 3-day workshop...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>IRREVERENTE - International Impro Festival of Lisbon</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/IRREVERENTE_-_International_Impro_Festival_of_Lisbon_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/IRREVERENTE_-_International_Impro_Festival_of_Lisbon_24</id>
   <updated>2024-07-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Festival intends to bring together the impro community living in Portugal with other countries, by promoting an event with activities in Theater, Dance, Music and other forms of art. In 2024 we introduce our Experimental Edition with the Theme: Impro and…&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>The Big Sing Musical Improv Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/The_Big_Sing_Musical_Improv_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/The_Big_Sing_Musical_Improv_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-06-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the second edition of The Big Sing Musical Improv Festival! Join us for 4 jam-packed days of musical workshops, shows, and improv fun in beautiful Barcelona, Spain. The Big Sing Musical Improv Festival brings together amateur and professional improvisers and musicians to teach, share, learn, celebrate, and enjoy...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Flock Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Flock_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Flock_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-06-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The international festival of Flock Theatre comes back with seven crazy days of improvised theatre, workshops, shows and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more information on the line-up of fabulous international teachers and performers soon!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Liverpool Improvisation Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-04-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;​Liverpool Improvisation Festival encourages innovation, risk taking and are inspired by those that do. The festival aims to create opportunity for those who create and teach improvised live performance at whatever stage of their career and across multiple art forms. In doing so we aim to educate, inspire and develop...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>ImproEM 2024 - European Championship in Improvised Theater</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/ImproEM_2024_-_European_Championship_in_Improvised_Theater_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/ImproEM_2024_-_European_Championship_in_Improvised_Theater_24</id>
   <updated>2024-04-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The ImproEM will be a European Improv Theater Championship with several matches in Munich (Germany) over four weeks in April/May 2024. Of 54 eligible European countries, we will select 18 teams to represent their nation and compete for the finals.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Application for mixed teams of three professional improv players for...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Edinburgh International Improv Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-02-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Back for a sixth edition, this beloved improv festival takes place in the heart of Scotland’s beautiful capital city, Edinburgh.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It’s four days of workshops, shows and late night jams. This year’s headliners are &lt;strong&gt;Holy Shit Improv’s Casey Feigh&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Suzi Barrett&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Ronnie Adrian&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;World’s Greatest Improv School’s Will...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>IMPRO Amsterdam</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/IMPRO_Amsterdam_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/IMPRO_Amsterdam_24</id>
   <updated>2024-02-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;IMPRO Amsterdam 2024 will rock Amsterdam Noord with eight days of high-quality international Improvisational Theatre! With 22 shows and more than 40 workshops, the festival is an incredible place to explore and learn about all different aspects of improv taught and performed by improvisers from all over the globe.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join...</content>
 </entry>

 

</feed>