<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Improv Festivals</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <updated>2024-11-27T00:04:38+00:00</updated>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <uri></uri>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Liverpool Improvisation Festival </title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_25"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_25</id>
   <updated>2025-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;LiF ​encourages innovation, risk taking and are inspired by those that do. The festival aims to create opportunity for those who create and teach improvised live performance at whatever stage of their career and across multiple art forms. In doing so we aim to educate, inspire and develop future audiences...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Auckland Improv Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Auckland_Improv_Festival_25"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Auckland_Improv_Festival_25</id>
   <updated>2025-04-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Auckland Improv Festival is all about showcasing and developing the art of improvisation. It’s community in spirit and professional in standards. AIF is a curated festival with expert teachers providing quality workshops and offers a diverse line up of shows from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>IMPRO Amsterdam</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/IMPRO_Amsterdam_25"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/IMPRO_Amsterdam_25</id>
   <updated>2025-02-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;impro-amsterdam-one-of-europes-biggest-and-longest-running-english-language-improv-festivals-is-turning-30&quot;&gt;IMPRO Amsterdam, one of Europe’s biggest and longest running English-language improv festivals, is turning 30!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;For eight days in February, IMPRO Amsterdam celebrates the breadth and diversity of not just what improv is, but what it can be - comedic, dramatic, abstract, experimental, lyrical, musical, physical, cozy, boundary-breaking, and...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>IFO Impro Fest</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_24</id>
   <updated>2024-10-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The IFO Impro Fest ist one of Germany´s biggest international festival with workshop, shows, party and a lot of improv fun!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Würzburger Improtheaterfestival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/W-C3-BCrzburger_Improtheaterfestival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/W%C3%BCrzburger_Improtheaterfestival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-10-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Würzburger Improtheaterfestival offers an intense weekend featuring extended workshops led by professional instructors from around the world, along with a varied show program. It has turned into a small, familiar and cosy festival with space and time for intensive work but also for real interpersonal contact.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>The REMIX Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/The_REMIX_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/The_REMIX_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Back for another year it’s the Reallygood Edinburgh Musical Improv eXtravaganza! Join us in Edinburgh 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿 from 18-20th October for an incredible weekend of musical improv classes and performances.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All of the workshops, shows, and jams are included in simple weekend passes so there’s no FOMO and you’ll get to...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Birmingham Improv Festival 2024</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Birmingham_Improv_Festival_2024_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Birmingham_Improv_Festival_2024_24</id>
   <updated>2024-10-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Birmingham’s Brilliant Biennial Improv Festival, bringing the best shows, teachers and improv fun to the UK’s Second City.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Das Improv Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Das_Improv_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Das_Improv_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-10-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Berlin’s long-form improv festival! Featuring the best alternative improv from across Europe and North America, with an exciting slate of headline acts from around the world and top-notch workshops and intensives, plus all the best improv Berlin itself has to offer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sign up for our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dasimprovfestival.com/newsletter/&quot;&gt;mailing list&lt;/a&gt; to get...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Sofia Improv Fest</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Sofia_Improv_Fest_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Sofia_Improv_Fest_24</id>
   <updated>2024-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;The festival will focus on a &lt;strong&gt;DEEP DIVE&lt;/strong&gt; into the realms of improv. The four original topics are:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;🦩 &lt;strong&gt;DEEP DIVE into Fun and Games&lt;/strong&gt;: We’re on the lookout for acts that will have our audience rolling with laughter. Bring on the joy, the silliness, and...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>MOMENTA - Impro Theater Festival International</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/MOMENTA_-_Impro_Theater_Festival_International_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/MOMENTA_-_Impro_Theater_Festival_International_24</id>
   <updated>2024-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Top-class international guests with innovative ideas and skills in improvisation, inspiring workshops, a hand-picked festival ensemble, shows, brand new improv formats, virtuosity and happenings - all this stands for a festival of special moments: MOMENTA!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

</feed>