<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Improv Festivals</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <updated>2023-12-12T00:01:54+00:00</updated>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <uri></uri>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Improfestival Karlsruhe</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_24</id>
   <updated>2024-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a smashing success in the last few years we are happy to be back in 2024 with even more shows and workshops.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This year we have a selection of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;12 ensemble-members (10 actors, 1 musician and 1 technician)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;A total of 9 days workshops, including one 3-day workshop...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Flock Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Flock_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Flock_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-06-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The international festival of Flock Theatre comes back with seven crazy days of improvised theatre, workshops, shows and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more information on the line-up of fabulous international teachers and performers soon!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Liverpool Improvisation Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_24</id>
   <updated>2024-04-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;​Liverpool Improvisation Festival encourages innovation, risk taking and are inspired by those that do. The festival aims to create opportunity for those who create and teach improvised live performance at whatever stage of their career and across multiple art forms. In doing so we aim to educate, inspire and develop...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>ImproEM 2024 - European Championship in Improvised Theater</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/ImproEM_2024_-_European_Championship_in_Improvised_Theater_24"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/ImproEM_2024_-_European_Championship_in_Improvised_Theater_24</id>
   <updated>2024-04-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The ImproEM will be a European Improv Theater Championship with several matches in Munich (Germany) over four weeks in April/May 2024. Of 54 eligible European countries, we will select 18 teams to represent their nation and compete for the finals.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Application for mixed teams of three professional improv players for...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Improv Fest Ireland</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23</id>
   <updated>2023-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ireland’s original international festival celebrating improvised theatre and comedy featuring workshops, shows, mixers and jams and probably the greatest improv after party in the world!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>IFO Impro Fest</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_23"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_23</id>
   <updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In March 2020, at the very beginning of the pandemic, Impro Fest Online started as the first digital festival for improvised theatre. Created in times of crisis, through the collaboration of actors from all over Germany and Austria, the IFO is a project from the community for the community. After...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Barcelona Improv Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Barcelona_Improv_Festival_23"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Barcelona_Improv_Festival_23</id>
   <updated>2023-10-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Barcelona Improv Festival is an annual celebration of European and worldwide improv, bringing together hundreds of improvisers from around the world to play, learn, and mix creatives from different cultures with diverse approaches to our art form. The festival is a mix of workshops during the day, performances by...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Improfest 2023</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Improfest_2023_23"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Improfest_2023_23</id>
   <updated>2023-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Improfest is the annual, international, inspirational, improvisational, dramational event where Mixed and United have invited impro groups from Belgium and the UK and, most importantly, YOU for three nights of laughter, tears and everything in between. The festival also includes workshops during the day, including stand-up comedy, physical theatre and...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Vancouver Improv Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/Vancouver_Improv_Festival_23"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/Vancouver_Improv_Festival_23</id>
   <updated>2023-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The 25th Vancouver Improv Fest takes place October 10-15, 2023. Featuring acts from North America and beyond, plus the Festival Ensemble! Festival includes 14 two-act shows, 15 public workshops, a panel and community events. Performer applications open May 15-June 30.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>The Remix Festival</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/The_Remix_Festival_23"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/The_Remix_Festival_23</id>
   <updated>2023-10-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This festival will be a full weekend of musical improv comedy joy! We’ve gathered four amazing teachers to come to Edinburgh and teach you the skills you’ll need to have the best possible time performing completely improvised musical comedy as part of short form, in your normal improv shows, or...</content>
 </entry>

 

</feed>