<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-14T00:02:22+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Improv Festivals</title><subtitle>&quot;Improv Festivals&quot; is a site to list impro festivals all over the world.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Improv Fest Ireland</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Improv Fest Ireland" /><published>2023-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23">&lt;p&gt;Ireland’s original international festival celebrating improvised theatre and comedy featuring workshops, shows, mixers and jams and probably the greatest improv after party in the world!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Ireland’s original international festival celebrating improvised theatre and comedy featuring workshops, shows, mixers and jams and probably the greatest improv after party in the world!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/Fb%20Crop%20-%20Neil%20Curran.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/Fb%20Crop%20-%20Neil%20Curran.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">IFO Impro Fest</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IFO Impro Fest" /><published>2023-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/IFO_Impro_Fest_23">&lt;p&gt;In March 2020, at the very beginning of the pandemic, Impro Fest Online started as the first digital festival for improvised theatre. Created in times of crisis, through the collaboration of actors from all over Germany and Austria, the IFO is a project from the community for the community. After more than 250 online workshops, our IFO landed in Bielefeld for the first time in October 2021 and celebrated a successful second offline edition in November 2022.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In March 2020, at the very beginning of the pandemic, Impro Fest Online started as the first digital festival for improvised theatre. Created in times of crisis, through the collaboration of actors from all over Germany and Austria, the IFO is a project from the community for the community. After more than 250 online workshops, our IFO landed in Bielefeld for the first time in October 2021 and celebrated a successful second offline edition in November 2022.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/Einfach%20Rahmen%20Fotografie%20Fotostudio%20Facebook-Titelbild%20-%20Lena%20Breuer.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/Einfach%20Rahmen%20Fotografie%20Fotostudio%20Facebook-Titelbild%20-%20Lena%20Breuer.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sofia International Improv Fest</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sofia International Improv Fest" /><published>2023-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23">&lt;p&gt;6-th International Sofia Improv Fest&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us in celebrating improv! 
​
Masterful and fun teachers with lots of experience to learn from and hone your skills
Lots of performance opportunities on our beautiful theatrical stage
Fun afterparties at our dedicated improv club with a bar
One of the friendliest improv communities in Europe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An optional hiking day to the beautiful Vitosha mountain&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of that at an affordable travel destination with great food and fun people! Check us out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;www.shizi.bg/soimprovfest&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">6-th International Sofia Improv Fest Join us in celebrating improv! ​ Masterful and fun teachers with lots of experience to learn from and hone your skills Lots of performance opportunities on our beautiful theatrical stage Fun afterparties at our dedicated improv club with a bar One of the friendliest improv communities in Europe An optional hiking day to the beautiful Vitosha mountain All of that at an affordable travel destination with great food and fun people! Check us out! www.shizi.bg/soimprovfest</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/Teaser_V%20-%20%D0%A8%D0%B8%D0%97%D0%B8%20%D0%98%D0%BC%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%20%D0%A2%D0%B5%D0%B0%D1%82%D1%8A%D1%80.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/Teaser_V%20-%20%D0%A8%D0%B8%D0%97%D0%B8%20%D0%98%D0%BC%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%BE%20%D0%A2%D0%B5%D0%B0%D1%82%D1%8A%D1%80.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Samothrace Improv Retreat</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Samothrace Improv Retreat" /><published>2023-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23">&lt;p&gt;A summer Intensive Retreat&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A summer Intensive Retreat</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/bannerforfestivalswebsite%20-%20Panagiotis%20Koudas.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/bannerforfestivalswebsite%20-%20Panagiotis%20Koudas.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">IRREVERENTE</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/IRREVERENTE_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IRREVERENTE" /><published>2023-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/IRREVERENTE_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/IRREVERENTE_23">&lt;p&gt;The Festival intends to bring together the impro community living in Portugal with other countries, by promoting an event with activities in Theater, Dance, Music and other forms of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our irreverence seeks to break preconceived concepts, about the art of improvisation and the art that is created in contemporaneity, questioning and reaffirming, and mainly, breaking with the idea that differences distance us. Saying “Yes, and”, the motto of improvisation. “Yes” for us and other people, “and” create together something that finds its own new rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Mission: Deconstruct judgments and preconceptions about art, ourselves and about the art we make, in order to find out authenticity at the rhythm of the Tejo river waves.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Festival intends to bring together the impro community living in Portugal with other countries, by promoting an event with activities in Theater, Dance, Music and other forms of art. Our irreverence seeks to break preconceived concepts, about the art of improvisation and the art that is created in contemporaneity, questioning and reaffirming, and mainly, breaking with the idea that differences distance us. Saying “Yes, and”, the motto of improvisation. “Yes” for us and other people, “and” create together something that finds its own new rules. Our Mission: Deconstruct judgments and preconceptions about art, ourselves and about the art we make, in order to find out authenticity at the rhythm of the Tejo river waves.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/Design%20sem%20nome%20%284%29%20-%20Irreverente%20Festival.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/Design%20sem%20nome%20%284%29%20-%20Irreverente%20Festival.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Pandora Improv Festival</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Pandora_Improv_Festival_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pandora Improv Festival" /><published>2023-06-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-06-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Pandora_Improv_Festival_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Pandora_Improv_Festival_23">&lt;p&gt;#PANDORA IMPROV FESTIVAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-days-of-music-love-and-improv&quot;&gt;3 days of music, love and improv&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pandora is an improv experience next to the seaside in Italy.
3 days full of events, workshops, shows, partytime, good food and wine, and much more!
All the students coming in Pandora have the same program: 9 or 12 hours workshops (mandatory for everyone!), team building activities, costume parties, main stage shows, late night shows (only for the braves), food and beverage, &lt;strong&gt;all inclusive&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;no sleep till Pandora!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">#PANDORA IMPROV FESTIVAL 3 days of music, love and improv Pandora is an improv experience next to the seaside in Italy. 3 days full of events, workshops, shows, partytime, good food and wine, and much more! All the students coming in Pandora have the same program: 9 or 12 hours workshops (mandatory for everyone!), team building activities, costume parties, main stage shows, late night shows (only for the braves), food and beverage, all inclusive no sleep till Pandora!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/logo%20pandora%20colori%20%281%29%20-%20Pandora%20Festival%20Improv.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/logo%20pandora%20colori%20%281%29%20-%20Pandora%20Festival%20Improv.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Mount Olymprov</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Mount_Olymprov_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mount Olymprov" /><published>2023-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Mount_Olymprov_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Mount_Olymprov_23">&lt;h2 id=&quot;welcome-to-mount-olymprov-festival&quot;&gt;Welcome to Mount Olymprov Festival&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a 3 year pause due to the pandemic, we are back, bigger and better than ever. With a lineup that will blow your mind, and activities that will make you fall in love with Greece, it is the obvious choice for next summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;with-a-stellar-lineup-of-11-instructors-and-16-different-shows-from-all-around-the-world&quot;&gt;With a stellar lineup of 11 instructors and 16 different shows from all around the world&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every year we make sure we bring you new talent to learn from, to enjoy mind-blowing improvised theater shows, to meet and socialize and live the full festival experience along 150+ improvisation enthusiasts from all corners of the planet.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome to Mount Olymprov Festival After a 3 year pause due to the pandemic, we are back, bigger and better than ever. With a lineup that will blow your mind, and activities that will make you fall in love with Greece, it is the obvious choice for next summer. With a stellar lineup of 11 instructors and 16 different shows from all around the world Every year we make sure we bring you new talent to learn from, to enjoy mind-blowing improvised theater shows, to meet and socialize and live the full festival experience along 150+ improvisation enthusiasts from all corners of the planet.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/improzeus-alone%20-%20Impro%20Festivals.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/improzeus-alone%20-%20Impro%20Festivals.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Auckland Improv Festival</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Auckland Improv Festival" /><published>2023-04-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23">&lt;p&gt;We have big news! We’re delighted to announce that international guest instructors Dan O’Connor, Patti Stiles Impro - official page and Andel Sudik will be joining us for the 2023 Auckland Improv Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The festival will take place in Auckland between April 11th and April 16th, 2023. During that week, we will have 10+ shows, 10+ workshops, masterclasses and social events for our participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hosted at the Covert Theatre in Ponsonby, the heart of Auckland City, the festival is directed by Matías Avaca and produced by Wade Jackson.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We have big news! We’re delighted to announce that international guest instructors Dan O’Connor, Patti Stiles Impro - official page and Andel Sudik will be joining us for the 2023 Auckland Improv Festival. The festival will take place in Auckland between April 11th and April 16th, 2023. During that week, we will have 10+ shows, 10+ workshops, masterclasses and social events for our participants. Hosted at the Covert Theatre in Ponsonby, the heart of Auckland City, the festival is directed by Matías Avaca and produced by Wade Jackson.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/309377273_518406533623658_353832290975872679_n%20-%20Mat%C3%ADas%20Avaca.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/309377273_518406533623658_353832290975872679_n%20-%20Mat%C3%ADas%20Avaca.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Edinburgh International Improv Festival</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Edinburgh International Improv Festival" /><published>2023-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23">&lt;p&gt;The Edinburgh International Improv Festival is held at the Scottish Storytelling Centre in Scotland’s beautiful capital city. It’s three days of workshops, shows and jams celebrating the best in improv from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this year’s festival we teamed up with World’s Greatest Improv School and had four of their teachers head across the pond to host workshops and perform.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Edinburgh International Improv Festival is held at the Scottish Storytelling Centre in Scotland’s beautiful capital city. It’s three days of workshops, shows and jams celebrating the best in improv from around the world. For this year’s festival we teamed up with World’s Greatest Improv School and had four of their teachers head across the pond to host workshops and perform.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/eiif%20-%20Impro%20Festivals.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/eiif%20-%20Impro%20Festivals.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Impro Amsterdam 2023</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impro Amsterdam 2023" /><published>2023-02-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-02-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23">&lt;p&gt;From the 25th of February to the 4th of March, IMPRO Amsterdam 2023 will rock Amsterdam Noord with eight days of high-quality international Improvisational Theatre. We have 29 shows from all over the world and 34 workshops that will teach you new skills or sharpen old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for a week and a day of the best Improv the international community has to offer and let’s make new friends from all over the world!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">From the 25th of February to the 4th of March, IMPRO Amsterdam 2023 will rock Amsterdam Noord with eight days of high-quality international Improvisational Theatre. We have 29 shows from all over the world and 34 workshops that will teach you new skills or sharpen old ones. Join us for a week and a day of the best Improv the international community has to offer and let’s make new friends from all over the world!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/impro_amsterdam%20-%20Impro%20Festivals.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://storage.googleapis.com/improfestivals_images/impro_amsterdam%20-%20Impro%20Festivals.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>