<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Improv Festivals</title>
        <description>Improv Festivals - </description>
        <link>https://improfestivals.com</link>
        <link>https://improfestivals.com</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2025-03-19T00:04:08+00:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2025-03-19T00:04:08+00:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Liverpool Improvisation Festival </title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;LiF ​encourages innovation, risk taking and are inspired by those that do. The festival aims to create opportunity for those who create and teach improvised live performance at whatever stage of their career and across multiple art forms. In doing so we aim to educate, inspire and develop future audiences and performers of improvisation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aim to produce a varied programme which is representative of the broad spectrum of improvised performance and community. This means we programme short and long form and work from new / emerging  artists / companies as well as those who are more established. We especially welcome applications from artists and companies who create work that is designed for children.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_25</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_25</guid>
                <pubDate>2025-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Auckland Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Auckland Improv Festival is all about showcasing and developing the art of improvisation. It’s community in spirit and professional in standards. AIF is a curated festival with expert teachers providing quality workshops and offers a diverse line up of shows from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Auckland_Improv_Festival_25</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Auckland_Improv_Festival_25</guid>
                <pubDate>2025-04-12T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Edinburgh International Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Taking place in the heart of Scotland’s beautiful capital city, the &lt;strong&gt;Edinburgh International Improv Festival&lt;/strong&gt; is back for year seven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a weekend filled with shows from teams near and far, workshops taught by incredible teachers, high energy late night jams, and a ton of memories made. And it’s all just a short walk down the hill from Edinburgh Castle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year’s headliners are &lt;strong&gt;Asian AF’s Jiavani&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Keiko Agena&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Lilan Bowden&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Convoy’s Alex Berg&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Todd Fasen&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Alex Fernie&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss out. Follow [@edimprovfest on Instagram] (https://www.instagram.com/edimprovfest/) for the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_25</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_25</guid>
                <pubDate>2025-03-20T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IMPRO Amsterdam</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;impro-amsterdam-one-of-europes-biggest-and-longest-running-english-language-improv-festivals-is-turning-30&quot;&gt;IMPRO Amsterdam, one of Europe’s biggest and longest running English-language improv festivals, is turning 30!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For eight days in February, IMPRO Amsterdam celebrates the breadth and diversity of not just what improv is, but what it can be - comedic, dramatic, abstract, experimental, lyrical, musical, physical, cozy, boundary-breaking, and everything in between. Come for the workshops, the shows, and the community; leave with your improv horizons permanently broadened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;featuring&quot;&gt;Featuring:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Several dozen shows and over fifty workshops featuring expert performers and teachers from five continents, as well as the best of the Netherlands&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A community centre where you can meet and play with over 150 improvisers from the Netherlands and around the world&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A leadership forum for theatre owners, producers, teachers, and organisers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Some secret birthday surprises…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay up to date on the festival by visiting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.impro-amsterdam.nl&quot;&gt;our website&lt;/a&gt; and signing up for our mailing list.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/IMPRO_Amsterdam_25</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/IMPRO_Amsterdam_25</guid>
                <pubDate>2025-02-15T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IFO Impro Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The IFO Impro Fest ist one of Germany´s biggest international festival with workshop, shows, party and a lot of improv fun!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/IFO_Impro_Fest_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/IFO_Impro_Fest_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-10-31T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Würzburger Improtheaterfestival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Würzburger Improtheaterfestival offers an intense weekend featuring extended workshops led by professional instructors from around the world, along with a varied show program. It has turned into a small, familiar and cosy festival with space and time for intensive work but also for real interpersonal contact.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/W-C3-BCrzburger_Improtheaterfestival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/W%C3%BCrzburger_Improtheaterfestival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-10-24T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The REMIX Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Back for another year it’s the Reallygood Edinburgh Musical Improv eXtravaganza! Join us in Edinburgh 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿 from 18-20th October for an incredible weekend of musical improv classes and performances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the workshops, shows, and jams are included in simple weekend passes  so there’s no FOMO and you’ll get to make loads of new improv pals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS. If you don’t like singing don’t worry, you can do a complete weekend of non musical improv classes with our teachers- we won’t judge you!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/The_REMIX_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/The_REMIX_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Birmingham Improv Festival 2024</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Birmingham’s Brilliant Biennial Improv Festival, bringing the best shows, teachers and improv fun to the UK’s Second City.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Birmingham_Improv_Festival_2024_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Birmingham_Improv_Festival_2024_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-10-09T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Das Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Berlin’s long-form improv festival! Featuring the best alternative improv from across Europe and North America, with an exciting slate of headline acts from around the world and top-notch workshops and intensives, plus all the best improv Berlin itself has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sign up for our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dasimprovfestival.com/newsletter/&quot;&gt;mailing list&lt;/a&gt; to get notified about Das news, including shows, ticket sales, workshops &amp;amp; more!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Das_Improv_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Das_Improv_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-10-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Sofia Improv Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The festival will focus on a &lt;strong&gt;DEEP DIVE&lt;/strong&gt; into the realms of improv. The four original topics are:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;🦩 &lt;strong&gt;DEEP DIVE into Fun and Games&lt;/strong&gt;: We’re on the lookout for acts that will have our audience rolling with laughter. Bring on the joy, the silliness, and the side-splitting humor!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;🌑 &lt;strong&gt;DEEP DIVE into Darkness&lt;/strong&gt;: Explore the shadows and mysteries of the stage and our craft.  Show us your skills in weaving tales of intrigue and suspense!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;🤸 &lt;strong&gt;DEEP DIVE into Physicality&lt;/strong&gt;: Move it, shake it, own the stage! We want performances that showcase the incredible power of the body in storytelling. Express yourself through the art of movement.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;🙂😥﻿🥰﻿﻿😠﻿ &lt;strong&gt;DEEP DIVE into Emotions&lt;/strong&gt;: Can you channel your inner actor?  Whether it’s laughter, tears, or everything in between – bring your A-game in evoking genuine feelings.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Sofia_Improv_Fest_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Sofia_Improv_Fest_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>MOMENTA - Impro Theater Festival International</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Top-class international guests with innovative ideas and skills in improvisation, inspiring workshops, a hand-picked festival ensemble, shows, brand new improv formats, virtuosity and happenings - all this stands for a festival of special moments: MOMENTA!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/MOMENTA_-_Impro_Theater_Festival_International_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/MOMENTA_-_Impro_Theater_Festival_International_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improvizza! </title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Improvizza! is a theatrical improvisation festival held in Malta, bringing together improvisers from all over the world to take workshops, play in jams, perform in showcases, watch shows and foster an improvisation community. Taking place on a tiny island in the middle of the Mediterranean, it offers a wonderful cultural, historical and artistic experience.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improvizza-21_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improvizza%21_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-09-04T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improfestival Karlsruhe</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;After a smashing success in the last few years we are happy to be back in 2024 with even more shows and workshops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This year we have a selection of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;12 ensemble-members (10 actors, 1 musician and 1 technician)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A total of 9 days workshops, including one 3-day workshop with a showcase&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And 18 completely different shows over 6 nights of performances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are very excited to have a put together a program of very different improvised styles that are represented in unique shows and workshops but at the same time to keep the spirit of a “cozy festival for friends”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to having you back or welcoming you for a first time in Karlsruhe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow us, get more info or book your tickets:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/improfestival.karlsruhe&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/improfestival.karlsruhe&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/ensemble&quot;&gt;About the ensemble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/shows&quot;&gt;Book your shows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/workshops&quot;&gt;Book your workshops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>ImproLyrik in der Wolkenburg</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us from August 23rd to 25th, 2024 at the börse Kulturzentrum, Wolkenburg in Wuppertal for an unforgettable weekend of improvisational theater infused with poetry and lyricism. Discover a world where words dance and scenes come alive with emotion. Featuring engaging workshops, captivating shows, and an atmosphere brimming with creativity, the ImproLyrik Festival promises an immersive experience like no other. Don’t miss out – get your tickets now at www.dieboerse-wtal.de/50-Jahre/ImproLyrik.php!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/ImproLyrik_in_der_Wolkenburg_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/ImproLyrik_in_der_Wolkenburg_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improfest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improfest_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improfest_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-08-19T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IRREVERENTE - International Impro Festival of Lisbon</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Festival intends to bring together the impro community living in Portugal with other countries, by promoting an event with activities in Theater, Dance, Music and other forms of art. In 2024 we introduce our Experimental Edition with the Theme: Impro and…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/IRREVERENTE_-_International_Impro_Festival_of_Lisbon_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/IRREVERENTE_-_International_Impro_Festival_of_Lisbon_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-07-24T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Big Sing Musical Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the second edition of The Big Sing Musical Improv Festival! Join us for 4 jam-packed days of musical workshops, shows, and improv fun in beautiful Barcelona, Spain. The Big Sing Musical Improv Festival brings together amateur and professional improvisers and musicians to teach, share, learn, celebrate, and enjoy the hilarious and magical art of musical improv&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applications to perform with your group open February 1st-21st
Workshop info &amp;amp; ticket sales to follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All details and updates will be posted at www.thebigsing.es&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/The_Big_Sing_Musical_Improv_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/The_Big_Sing_Musical_Improv_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-06-26T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Flock Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The international festival of Flock Theatre comes back with seven crazy days of improvised theatre, workshops, shows and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more information on the line-up of fabulous international teachers and performers soon!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Flock_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Flock_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-06-24T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Close Encounters Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to be planning this festival that we hope will happen every year from 2024-infinity! The purpose of the festival is to celebrate improv and artists and to unite artists from all over Switzerland and eventually the world! We also want to have a lot of fun and parties! :) The theme will be 80’s inspired and our first festival is entitled BACK to the FUTURE! 
Stay tuned! 
https://www.closeencounterstheatre.com/festival-june-2024&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Close_Encounters_Improv_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Close_Encounters_Improv_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-06-21T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improvaganza</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Produced by Rapid Fire Theatre, Improvaganza is Edmonton’s international improv and sketch comedy festival featuring improvisers from around the world! This festival was created in 2001. &lt;a href=&quot;https://rapidfiretheatre.com/past-improvaganzas/&quot;&gt;Check out our archive of past festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improvaganza_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improvaganza_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-06-20T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>BUENA ONDA FEST</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;¡Buena Onda - International Improvisational Theater Festival!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bogotá vibrates with this grand celebration of improvisation. Enjoy a fantastic collection of diverse shows. We will start with Maestro™, a classic format perfect for inaugurating this celebration, where 14 improvisers compete to become the winner of the night. Then, we immerse ourselves in a format where a cast of women will share personal experiences. An original creation by Hila De Castro that will be presented simultaneously in different cities around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, the group behind La Terapia will delight us with a show born from last year’s New Formats Laboratory. In a double feature night, we will close with a flourish presenting Directors Cut, a competition between directors that will leave you breathless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, March 16, this improvisation marathon culminates with an explosive day. Two workshops led by our international guests and another double feature. The ensemble premieres Chorizo, a format of particular connections, tied by a space, and we finish the day with the fabulous Moments of Life, an original format by Patti Stiles that always takes us to fascinating places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year we have the presence of a great guest visiting us from Slovenia and another great colleague coming from Italy. Sara Šoukal (Ljubljana), a very important figure in international theatrical improvisation, who has been exploring clowning, street theater, contemporary dance, among others, for some time, and Andrea Lagrange (Rome), a passionate improviser and teacher who seeks to develop an expressive body language and create captivating relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/BUENA_ONDA_FEST_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/BUENA_ONDA_FEST_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-05-13T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Liverpool Improvisation Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;​Liverpool Improvisation Festival encourages innovation, risk taking and are inspired by those that do. The festival aims to create opportunity for those who create and teach improvised live performance at whatever stage of their career and across multiple art forms. In doing so we aim to educate, inspire and develop future audiences and performers of improvisation.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-04-19T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>ImproEM 2024 - European Championship in Improvised Theater</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The ImproEM will be a European Improv Theater Championship with several matches in Munich (Germany) over four weeks in April/May 2024. Of 54 eligible European countries, we will select 18 teams to represent their nation and compete for the finals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Application for mixed teams of three professional improv players for these paid gigs (incl. accommodation and transport) are open through September 2023. We are looking forward to welcoming the European Improv Community in Munich!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants should hold a passport of the nation they seek to represent at the games. Please visit our website for all details.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/ImproEM_2024_-_European_Championship_in_Improvised_Theater_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/ImproEM_2024_-_European_Championship_in_Improvised_Theater_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-04-17T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Little Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;After a hugely success inaugural event last year, The Bristol Improv Theatre are delighted to announce the return of The Little Improv Festival for 2024! Join us on Friday 22nd March for the festival launch, followed by an all day festival on 23rd March.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expect exciting entertainment from Bristol’s best improvisers, a chance or two to give improv a go yourself, a warm welcome in our cosy bar between shows and lots more from the friendliest theatre in town!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/The_Little_Improv_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/The_Little_Improv_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Edinburgh International Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Back for a sixth edition, this beloved improv festival takes place in the heart of Scotland’s beautiful capital city, Edinburgh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s four days of workshops, shows and late night jams. This year’s headliners are &lt;strong&gt;Holy Shit Improv’s Casey Feigh&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Suzi Barrett&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Ronnie Adrian&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;World’s Greatest Improv School’s Will Hines&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Sarah Claspell&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Jim Woods&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joining them are long time UCB performers and teachers &lt;strong&gt;Monika Smith&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Billy Merritt&lt;/strong&gt; coaching this year’s Ensemble team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a celebration of all things long form improv you won’t want to miss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/edimprovfest/&quot;&gt;@edimprovfest on Instagram&lt;/a&gt; for the latest updates&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-02-29T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IMPRO Amsterdam</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;IMPRO Amsterdam 2024 will rock Amsterdam Noord with eight days of high-quality international Improvisational Theatre! With 22 shows and more than 40 workshops, the festival is an incredible place to explore and learn about all different aspects of improv taught and performed by improvisers from all over the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for 8 days of the best Improv the international community has to offer and let’s make new friends from all over the world!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://impro-amsterdam.nl/events/shows&quot;&gt;Shows&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://impro-amsterdam.nl/events/workshops&quot;&gt;Workshops&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/IMPROAmsterdam/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/improamsterdam/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/IMPRO_Amsterdam_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/IMPRO_Amsterdam_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-02-17T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improv Fest Ireland</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Ireland’s original international festival celebrating improvised theatre and comedy featuring workshops, shows, mixers and jams and probably the greatest improv after party in the world!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IFO Impro Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;In March 2020, at the very beginning of the pandemic, Impro Fest Online started as the first digital festival for improvised theatre. Created in times of crisis, through the collaboration of actors from all over Germany and Austria, the IFO is a project from the community for the community. After more than 250 online workshops, our IFO landed in Bielefeld for the first time in October 2021 and celebrated a successful second offline edition in November 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/IFO_Impro_Fest_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/IFO_Impro_Fest_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Barcelona Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Barcelona Improv Festival is an annual celebration of European and worldwide improv, bringing together hundreds of improvisers from around the world to play, learn, and mix creatives from different cultures with diverse approaches to our art form. The festival is a mix of workshops during the day, performances by invited teams and mixer teams at night, and social events throughout the week.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Barcelona_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Barcelona_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-10-25T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improfest 2023</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Improfest is the annual, international, inspirational, improvisational, dramational event where Mixed and United have invited impro groups from Belgium and the UK and, most importantly, YOU for three nights of laughter, tears and everything in between. The festival also includes workshops during the day, including stand-up comedy, physical theatre and impro fundamentals.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improfest_2023_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improfest_2023_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Vancouver Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The 25th Vancouver Improv Fest takes place October 10-15, 2023. Featuring acts from North America and beyond, plus the Festival Ensemble! Festival includes 14 two-act shows, 15 public workshops, a panel and community events. Performer applications open May 15-June 30.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Vancouver_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Vancouver_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Remix Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;This festival will be a full weekend of musical improv comedy joy! We’ve gathered four amazing teachers to come to Edinburgh and teach you the skills you’ll need to have the best possible time performing completely improvised musical comedy as part of short form, in your normal improv shows, or as a fully improvised musical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will have a huge range of musical class topics, as well as classes about core improv skills (no singing required!). Each class will be limited to max 16 people so you will get plenty of time practicing in each class and lots of individual feedback from your teachers. We will also have amazing shows and jams every night.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/The_Remix_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/The_Remix_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-10-06T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Das Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Berlin’s first festival for long-form improv organised in collaboration with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comedycafeberlin.com/&quot;&gt;Comedy Cafe berlin&lt;/a&gt; first took place in 2019 and restarted in 2023 after a short break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The festival features teams from across Europe and North America with an exciting slate of headline acts from around the world and top-notch workshops and intensives, plus all the best improv Berlin itself has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dasimprovfestival.com/newsletter/&quot;&gt;Sign up for our mailing&lt;/a&gt; list to get notified about Das news, including shows, ticket sales, workshops &amp;amp; more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dasimprovfestival.com/festival-application/&quot;&gt;Performer applications&lt;/a&gt; are generally open from June to July.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Das_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Das_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Sofia International Improv Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;We are happy to invite you to the 6-th International Sofia Improv Festival. 
20-24 September 2023, Sofia, Bulgaria&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENRES&lt;/strong&gt; is the topic of this year’s festival. Join us in celebrating improv!
Four groups will perform four different improv shows in distinct genres. The performers will be teaching master classes in the respective genres 
during the festival. Additional workshops will be available for honing your improv skills. There will be lots of performance opportunities on our beautiful theatrical stage. 
Fun afterparties will shake our bar at the dedicated ShiZi Improv Club. 
Come meet one of the friendliest improv communities in Europe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An optional hiking day to the beautiful Vitosha mountain just half hour away from the city. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An affordable travel destination with great food and fun people! Check us out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shizi.bg/soimprovfest&quot;&gt;www.shizi.bg/soimprovfest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/soimprovfest/&quot;&gt;www.facebook.com/soimprovfest/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>12. Düsseldorfer Improtheaterfestival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Ein liebevoller Raum für Begegnungen und gemeinsames Arbeiten, zusammen lachen, staunen und fühlen. Mitten in Düsseldorf. Das ist das Düsseldorfer Improtheater-Festival, das auch in diesem Jahr wieder stattfinden wird!
Die Phönixallee – Düsseldorfs erstes Improtheater – freut sich im September 2023 wieder auf Gäste aus allen Himmelsrichtungen.
Auf dem Programm stehen:
drei thematisch völlig unterschiedliche Workshops bei fantastischen Trainer*innen
eine Session, bei der sich alle auf die Bühne wagen und gemeinsam improvisieren können,
gemeinsame Abende in der Stadt an der längsten Theke der Welt und zum Abschluss der große Impro-Wettstreit im legendären Kom(m)ödchen: Der Goldene Phön!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/12._D-C3-BCsseldorfer_Improtheaterfestival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/12._D%C3%BCsseldorfer_Improtheaterfestival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-09-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improfestival Karlsruhe</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;After a smashing success in 2022 we are happy to be back in 2023 with even more shows and workshops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This year we have a selection of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11 ensemble-members (10 actors and actresses and 1 musician)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A total of 13 workshops&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And 15 completely different shows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are very excited to have a put together a program of very different improvised styles that are represented in unique shows and workshops but at the same time to keep the spirit of a “cozy festival for friends”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to having you back or welcoming you for a first time in Karlsruhe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow us, get more info or book your tickets:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/improfestival.karlsruhe&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/improfestival.karlsruhe&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/ensemble&quot;&gt;About the ensemble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/shows&quot;&gt;Book your shows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/workshops&quot;&gt;Book your workshops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-08-29T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Lyon Improv Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Through the Lyon Improv Fest, we want to create a shared experience of transcendence, where performers and audience members come together to create something greater than themselves. This can lead to a sense of community and connectedness, as well as a deeper understanding of ourselves and our place in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Lyon_Improv_Fest_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Lyon_Improv_Fest_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Samothrace Improv Retreat</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A summer Intensive Retreat&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Big Sing Musical Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;26th - 30th  JULY 2023 
4 jam-packed days of musical workshops, shows, and improv fun in beautiful BARCELONA, SPAIN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SHOWS &amp;amp; WORKSHOPS
with STACEY SMITH, HEATHER URQUHART, JOE SAMUEL,  SACHA HOEDEMAKER, LARRY DORSEY JR, &amp;amp; MORE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;APPLY TO PERFORM 
Applications to perform with your group open  MARCH 1ST 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/The_Big_Sing_Musical_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/The_Big_Sing_Musical_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IRREVERENTE</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Festival intends to bring together the impro community living in Portugal with other countries, by promoting an event with activities in Theater, Dance, Music and other forms of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our irreverence seeks to break preconceived concepts, about the art of improvisation and the art that is created in contemporaneity, questioning and reaffirming, and mainly, breaking with the idea that differences distance us. Saying “Yes, and”, the motto of improvisation. “Yes” for us and other people, “and” create together something that finds its own new rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Mission: Deconstruct judgments and preconceptions about art, ourselves and about the art we make, in order to find out authenticity at the rhythm of the Tejo river waves.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/IRREVERENTE_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/IRREVERENTE_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Tolfama - International Festival of Improvised Arts</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The International Festival of Improvised Arts – Tolfama, is an event organized by the National School of Improvisation and Theater Vicolo Cechov. Now in its twelfth edition, it is considered one of the most important “Site Specific Theatre” festivals nationally and internationally. It features workshops with internationally renowned theatre improvisation teachers, site-specific and street art performances, improvised craft stands, good food and wine, parties and relax in one of the most charming and full of history italian villages. Tolfama is the perfect combination of quality workshops and entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Tolfama_-_International_Festival_of_Improvised_Arts_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Tolfama_-_International_Festival_of_Improvised_Arts_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Flock Festival - Project 2x2 mini-festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;At Flock Theatre, we love working with other artists from all over the world. Katy Schutte and Chris Mead are two fantastic improvisers from the United Kingdoms: they are accomplished multi-talented artists, great teachers and brilliant performers. They are also our friends!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this edition of our Flock Festival, we—Laura and Gael Doorneweerd-Perry—are inviting them for a week to work with us on different things:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Giving public workshops for a week, from half-a-day to two-day long&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Performing their brilliant duo-show already existing, Hopepunk / Project 2&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Working in residency for 5 days with Laura and Gael in order to design &lt;strong&gt;four brand new fully improvised shows&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Showcasing two nights of shows—3 shows a night—the result of the work: unique and exclusive duo-shows as well as the world-renowned Project 2 and Object of Affection!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can join in by taking workshops and joining shows, as well as meeting the fantastic Amsterdam community for this big improv feast!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Flock_Festival_-_Project_2x2_mini-festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Flock_Festival_-_Project_2x2_mini-festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-06-17T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Pandora Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;#PANDORA IMPROV FESTIVAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-days-of-music-love-and-improv&quot;&gt;3 days of music, love and improv&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pandora is an improv experience next to the seaside in Italy.
3 days full of events, workshops, shows, partytime, good food and wine, and much more!
All the students coming in Pandora have the same program: 9 or 12 hours workshops (mandatory for everyone!), team building activities, costume parties, main stage shows, late night shows (only for the braves), food and beverage, &lt;strong&gt;all inclusive&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;no sleep till Pandora!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Pandora_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Pandora_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-06-09T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Mount Olymprov</title>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;welcome-to-mount-olymprov-festival&quot;&gt;Welcome to Mount Olymprov Festival&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a 3 year pause due to the pandemic, we are back, bigger and better than ever. With a lineup that will blow your mind, and activities that will make you fall in love with Greece, it is the obvious choice for next summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;with-a-stellar-lineup-of-11-instructors-and-16-different-shows-from-all-around-the-world&quot;&gt;With a stellar lineup of 11 instructors and 16 different shows from all around the world&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every year we make sure we bring you new talent to learn from, to enjoy mind-blowing improvised theater shows, to meet and socialize and live the full festival experience along 150+ improvisation enthusiasts from all corners of the planet.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Mount_Olymprov_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Mount_Olymprov_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Auckland Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;We have big news! We’re delighted to announce that international guest instructors Dan O’Connor, Patti Stiles Impro - official page and Andel Sudik will be joining us for the 2023 Auckland Improv Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The festival will take place in Auckland between April 11th and April 16th, 2023. During that week, we will have 10+ shows, 10+ workshops, masterclasses and social events for our participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hosted at the Covert Theatre in Ponsonby, the heart of Auckland City, the festival is directed by Matías Avaca and produced by Wade Jackson.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-04-11T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Short Notice Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to seven days of live comedy, great workshops and community!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It even has the full Norwegian wood experience, the BIG DAY OUT!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Short_Notice_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Short_Notice_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Edinburgh International Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Edinburgh International Improv Festival is held at the Scottish Storytelling Centre in Scotland’s beautiful capital city. It’s three days of workshops, shows and jams celebrating the best in improv from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this year’s festival we teamed up with World’s Greatest Improv School and had four of their teachers head across the pond to host workshops and perform.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Impro Amsterdam 2023</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;From the 25th of February to the 4th of March, IMPRO Amsterdam 2023 will rock Amsterdam Noord with eight days of high-quality international Improvisational Theatre. We have 29 shows from all over the world and 34 workshops that will teach you new skills or sharpen old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for a week and a day of the best Improv the international community has to offer and let’s make new friends from all over the world!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-25T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Moth & Butterfly International Festival of Storytelling & Improvisation</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Moth &amp;amp; Butterfly International Festival of Storytelling &amp;amp; Improvisation is an Arts festival based in Galway in the West of Ireland. Our first festival was in 2021 and was presented digitally, in 2022 was hybrid with live events and the 2023 festival will be fully live from Galway, while retaining digital content for our international audiences. The festival will feature shows, workshops, arts events, story swaps, children’s events and bilingual presentations.  The festival highlights the artforms of improvisation and storytelling in all their presentations, and is particularly interested in the magical places where they intersect. The festival features local, national and international professional artists, as well as community participation. The festival is produced by Aoife Demel, with Artistic Director Órla Mc Govern, and core M &amp;amp; B crew members. Join our mailing list at www.mothandbutterflystories.com&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Moth_&_Butterfly_International_Festival_of_Storytelling_&_Improvisation_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Moth_&_Butterfly_International_Festival_of_Storytelling_&_Improvisation_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>SPUNK</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;theater anundpfirsich invites you to the 10th and last edition of SPUNK, the Zurich Improtheater Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From October 10 to 16, 2022, the festival ensemble shows with top-class guests from the USA, Great Britain, Poland, Germany, the Netherlands, Austria, Slovenia and Switzerland what improvised theater has to offer. The audience will be immersed in the exciting, spontaneous and multifaceted world of improvised theater. On the stage of the new Theater im Zollhaus completely surprising stories and characters emerge from the moment. A unique and one-of-a-kind theater experience, created for one evening only.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/SPUNK_22</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/SPUNK_22</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title></title>
                <description>
</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/_01</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/_01</guid>
                <pubDate>0001-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
