<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Improv Festivals</title>
        <description>Improv Festivals - </description>
        <link>https://improfestivals.com</link>
        <link>https://improfestivals.com</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2022-11-26T13:53:22+00:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2022-11-26T13:53:22+00:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Edinburgh International Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Edinburgh International Improv Festival is held at the Scottish Storytelling Centre in Scotland’s beautiful capital city. It’s three days of workshops, shows and jams celebrating the best in improv from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this year’s festival we teamed up with World’s Greatest Improv School and had four of their teachers head across the pond to host workshops and perform.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Impro Amsterdam 2023</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;From the 25th of February to the 4th of March, IMPRO Amsterdam 2023 will rock Amsterdam Noord with eight days of high-quality international Improvisational Theatre. We have 29 shows from all over the world and 34 workshops that will teach you new skills or sharpen old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for a week and a day of the best Improv the international community has to offer and let’s make new friends from all over the world!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-25T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Moth & Butterfly Int'l Festival of Storytelling & Improvisation </title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Kindly funded by The Arts Council of Ireland and Galway City Council.
Please stay tuned and sign up to our mailing list (via the link at the bottom of the page) for updates about our 2023 Festival as well as all of our regular events and future projects.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Moth_&_Butterfly_Int-27l_Festival_of_Storytelling_&_Improvisation_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Moth_&_Butterfly_Int%27l_Festival_of_Storytelling_&_Improvisation_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>SPUNK</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;theater anundpfirsich invites you to the 10th and last edition of SPUNK, the Zurich Improtheater Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From October 10 to 16, 2022, the festival ensemble shows with top-class guests from the USA, Great Britain, Poland, Germany, the Netherlands, Austria, Slovenia and Switzerland what improvised theater has to offer. The audience will be immersed in the exciting, spontaneous and multifaceted world of improvised theater. On the stage of the new Theater im Zollhaus completely surprising stories and characters emerge from the moment. A unique and one-of-a-kind theater experience, created for one evening only.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/SPUNK_22</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/SPUNK_22</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
