<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Improv Festivals</title>
        <description>Improv Festivals - </description>
        <link>https://improfestivals.com</link>
        <link>https://improfestivals.com</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2023-08-18T00:02:50+00:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2023-08-18T00:02:50+00:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Liverpool Improvisation Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;​Liverpool Improvisation Festival encourages innovation, risk taking and are inspired by those that do. The festival aims to create opportunity for those who create and teach improvised live performance at whatever stage of their career and across multiple art forms. In doing so we aim to educate, inspire and develop future audiences and performers of improvisation.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_24</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Liverpool_Improvisation_Festival_24</guid>
                <pubDate>2024-04-19T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improv Fest Ireland</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Ireland’s original international festival celebrating improvised theatre and comedy featuring workshops, shows, mixers and jams and probably the greatest improv after party in the world!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IFO Impro Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;In March 2020, at the very beginning of the pandemic, Impro Fest Online started as the first digital festival for improvised theatre. Created in times of crisis, through the collaboration of actors from all over Germany and Austria, the IFO is a project from the community for the community. After more than 250 online workshops, our IFO landed in Bielefeld for the first time in October 2021 and celebrated a successful second offline edition in November 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/IFO_Impro_Fest_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/IFO_Impro_Fest_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Barcelona Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Barcelona Improv Festival is an annual celebration of European and worldwide improv, bringing together hundreds of improvisers from around the world to play, learn, and mix creatives from different cultures with diverse approaches to our art form. The festival is a mix of workshops during the day, performances by invited teams and mixer teams at night, and social events throughout the week.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Barcelona_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Barcelona_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-10-25T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Vancouver Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The 25th Vancouver Improv Fest takes place October 10-15, 2023. Featuring acts from North America and beyond, plus the Festival Ensemble! Festival includes 14 two-act shows, 15 public workshops, a panel and community events. Performer applications open May 15-June 30.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Vancouver_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Vancouver_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Remix Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;This festival will be a full weekend of musical improv comedy joy! We’ve gathered four amazing teachers to come to Edinburgh and teach you the skills you’ll need to have the best possible time performing completely improvised musical comedy as part of short form, in your normal improv shows, or as a fully improvised musical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will have a huge range of musical class topics, as well as classes about core improv skills (no singing required!). Each class will be limited to max 16 people so you will get plenty of time practicing in each class and lots of individual feedback from your teachers. We will also have amazing shows and jams every night.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/The_Remix_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/The_Remix_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-10-06T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Das Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Berlin’s first festival for long-form improv organised in collaboration with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comedycafeberlin.com/&quot;&gt;Comedy Cafe berlin&lt;/a&gt; first took place in 2019 and restarted in 2023 after a short break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The festival features teams from across Europe and North America with an exciting slate of headline acts from around the world and top-notch workshops and intensives, plus all the best improv Berlin itself has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dasimprovfestival.com/newsletter/&quot;&gt;Sign up for our mailing&lt;/a&gt; list to get notified about Das news, including shows, ticket sales, workshops &amp;amp; more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dasimprovfestival.com/festival-application/&quot;&gt;Performer applications&lt;/a&gt; are generally open from June to July.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Das_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Das_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Sofia International Improv Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;We are happy to invite you to the 6-th International Sofia Improv Festival. 
20-24 September 2023, Sofia, Bulgaria&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENRES&lt;/strong&gt; is the topic of this year’s festival. Join us in celebrating improv!
Four groups will perform four different improv shows in distinct genres. The performers will be teaching master classes in the respective genres 
during the festival. Additional workshops will be available for honing your improv skills. There will be lots of performance opportunities on our beautiful theatrical stage. 
Fun afterparties will shake our bar at the dedicated ShiZi Improv Club. 
Come meet one of the friendliest improv communities in Europe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An optional hiking day to the beautiful Vitosha mountain just half hour away from the city. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An affordable travel destination with great food and fun people! Check us out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shizi.bg/soimprovfest&quot;&gt;www.shizi.bg/soimprovfest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/soimprovfest/&quot;&gt;www.facebook.com/soimprovfest/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>12. Düsseldorfer Improtheaterfestival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Ein liebevoller Raum für Begegnungen und gemeinsames Arbeiten, zusammen lachen, staunen und fühlen. Mitten in Düsseldorf. Das ist das Düsseldorfer Improtheater-Festival, das auch in diesem Jahr wieder stattfinden wird!
Die Phönixallee – Düsseldorfs erstes Improtheater – freut sich im September 2023 wieder auf Gäste aus allen Himmelsrichtungen.
Auf dem Programm stehen:
drei thematisch völlig unterschiedliche Workshops bei fantastischen Trainer*innen
eine Session, bei der sich alle auf die Bühne wagen und gemeinsam improvisieren können,
gemeinsame Abende in der Stadt an der längsten Theke der Welt und zum Abschluss der große Impro-Wettstreit im legendären Kom(m)ödchen: Der Goldene Phön!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/12._D-C3-BCsseldorfer_Improtheaterfestival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/12._D%C3%BCsseldorfer_Improtheaterfestival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-09-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improfestival Karlsruhe</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;After a smashing success in 2022 we are happy to be back in 2023 with even more shows and workshops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This year we have a selection of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11 ensemble-members (10 actors and actresses and 1 musician)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A total of 13 workshops&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And 15 completely different shows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are very excited to have a put together a program of very different improvised styles that are represented in unique shows and workshops but at the same time to keep the spirit of a “cozy festival for friends”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to having you back or welcoming you for a first time in Karlsruhe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow us, get more info or book your tickets:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/improfestival.karlsruhe&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/improfestival.karlsruhe&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/ensemble&quot;&gt;About the ensemble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/shows&quot;&gt;Book your shows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.improfestival-karlsruhe.com/workshops&quot;&gt;Book your workshops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improfestival_Karlsruhe_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-08-29T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Lyon Improv Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Through the Lyon Improv Fest, we want to create a shared experience of transcendence, where performers and audience members come together to create something greater than themselves. This can lead to a sense of community and connectedness, as well as a deeper understanding of ourselves and our place in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Lyon_Improv_Fest_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Lyon_Improv_Fest_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-08-20T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Samothrace Improv Retreat</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A summer Intensive Retreat&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Big Sing Musical Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;26th - 30th  JULY 2023 
4 jam-packed days of musical workshops, shows, and improv fun in beautiful BARCELONA, SPAIN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SHOWS &amp;amp; WORKSHOPS
with STACEY SMITH, HEATHER URQUHART, JOE SAMUEL,  SACHA HOEDEMAKER, LARRY DORSEY JR, &amp;amp; MORE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;APPLY TO PERFORM 
Applications to perform with your group open  MARCH 1ST 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/The_Big_Sing_Musical_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/The_Big_Sing_Musical_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IRREVERENTE</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Festival intends to bring together the impro community living in Portugal with other countries, by promoting an event with activities in Theater, Dance, Music and other forms of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our irreverence seeks to break preconceived concepts, about the art of improvisation and the art that is created in contemporaneity, questioning and reaffirming, and mainly, breaking with the idea that differences distance us. Saying “Yes, and”, the motto of improvisation. “Yes” for us and other people, “and” create together something that finds its own new rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Mission: Deconstruct judgments and preconceptions about art, ourselves and about the art we make, in order to find out authenticity at the rhythm of the Tejo river waves.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/IRREVERENTE_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/IRREVERENTE_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Tolfama - International Festival of Improvised Arts</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The International Festival of Improvised Arts – Tolfama, is an event organized by the National School of Improvisation and Theater Vicolo Cechov. Now in its twelfth edition, it is considered one of the most important “Site Specific Theatre” festivals nationally and internationally. It features workshops with internationally renowned theatre improvisation teachers, site-specific and street art performances, improvised craft stands, good food and wine, parties and relax in one of the most charming and full of history italian villages. Tolfama is the perfect combination of quality workshops and entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Tolfama_-_International_Festival_of_Improvised_Arts_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Tolfama_-_International_Festival_of_Improvised_Arts_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Flock Festival - Project 2x2 mini-festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;At Flock Theatre, we love working with other artists from all over the world. Katy Schutte and Chris Mead are two fantastic improvisers from the United Kingdoms: they are accomplished multi-talented artists, great teachers and brilliant performers. They are also our friends!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this edition of our Flock Festival, we—Laura and Gael Doorneweerd-Perry—are inviting them for a week to work with us on different things:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Giving public workshops for a week, from half-a-day to two-day long&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Performing their brilliant duo-show already existing, Hopepunk / Project 2&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Working in residency for 5 days with Laura and Gael in order to design &lt;strong&gt;four brand new fully improvised shows&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Showcasing two nights of shows—3 shows a night—the result of the work: unique and exclusive duo-shows as well as the world-renowned Project 2 and Object of Affection!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can join in by taking workshops and joining shows, as well as meeting the fantastic Amsterdam community for this big improv feast!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Flock_Festival_-_Project_2x2_mini-festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Flock_Festival_-_Project_2x2_mini-festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-06-17T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Pandora Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;#PANDORA IMPROV FESTIVAL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-days-of-music-love-and-improv&quot;&gt;3 days of music, love and improv&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pandora is an improv experience next to the seaside in Italy.
3 days full of events, workshops, shows, partytime, good food and wine, and much more!
All the students coming in Pandora have the same program: 9 or 12 hours workshops (mandatory for everyone!), team building activities, costume parties, main stage shows, late night shows (only for the braves), food and beverage, &lt;strong&gt;all inclusive&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;no sleep till Pandora!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Pandora_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Pandora_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-06-09T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Mount Olymprov</title>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;welcome-to-mount-olymprov-festival&quot;&gt;Welcome to Mount Olymprov Festival&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a 3 year pause due to the pandemic, we are back, bigger and better than ever. With a lineup that will blow your mind, and activities that will make you fall in love with Greece, it is the obvious choice for next summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;with-a-stellar-lineup-of-11-instructors-and-16-different-shows-from-all-around-the-world&quot;&gt;With a stellar lineup of 11 instructors and 16 different shows from all around the world&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every year we make sure we bring you new talent to learn from, to enjoy mind-blowing improvised theater shows, to meet and socialize and live the full festival experience along 150+ improvisation enthusiasts from all corners of the planet.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Mount_Olymprov_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Mount_Olymprov_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Auckland Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;We have big news! We’re delighted to announce that international guest instructors Dan O’Connor, Patti Stiles Impro - official page and Andel Sudik will be joining us for the 2023 Auckland Improv Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The festival will take place in Auckland between April 11th and April 16th, 2023. During that week, we will have 10+ shows, 10+ workshops, masterclasses and social events for our participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hosted at the Covert Theatre in Ponsonby, the heart of Auckland City, the festival is directed by Matías Avaca and produced by Wade Jackson.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-04-11T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Short Notice Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to seven days of live comedy, great workshops and community!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It even has the full Norwegian wood experience, the BIG DAY OUT!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Short_Notice_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Short_Notice_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Edinburgh International Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Edinburgh International Improv Festival is held at the Scottish Storytelling Centre in Scotland’s beautiful capital city. It’s three days of workshops, shows and jams celebrating the best in improv from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this year’s festival we teamed up with World’s Greatest Improv School and had four of their teachers head across the pond to host workshops and perform.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Impro Amsterdam 2023</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;From the 25th of February to the 4th of March, IMPRO Amsterdam 2023 will rock Amsterdam Noord with eight days of high-quality international Improvisational Theatre. We have 29 shows from all over the world and 34 workshops that will teach you new skills or sharpen old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for a week and a day of the best Improv the international community has to offer and let’s make new friends from all over the world!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-25T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Moth & Butterfly International Festival of Storytelling & Improvisation</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Moth &amp;amp; Butterfly International Festival of Storytelling &amp;amp; Improvisation is an Arts festival based in Galway in the West of Ireland. Our first festival was in 2021 and was presented digitally, in 2022 was hybrid with live events and the 2023 festival will be fully live from Galway, while retaining digital content for our international audiences. The festival will feature shows, workshops, arts events, story swaps, children’s events and bilingual presentations.  The festival highlights the artforms of improvisation and storytelling in all their presentations, and is particularly interested in the magical places where they intersect. The festival features local, national and international professional artists, as well as community participation. The festival is produced by Aoife Demel, with Artistic Director Órla Mc Govern, and core M &amp;amp; B crew members. Join our mailing list at www.mothandbutterflystories.com&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Moth_&_Butterfly_International_Festival_of_Storytelling_&_Improvisation_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Moth_&_Butterfly_International_Festival_of_Storytelling_&_Improvisation_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>SPUNK</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;theater anundpfirsich invites you to the 10th and last edition of SPUNK, the Zurich Improtheater Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From October 10 to 16, 2022, the festival ensemble shows with top-class guests from the USA, Great Britain, Poland, Germany, the Netherlands, Austria, Slovenia and Switzerland what improvised theater has to offer. The audience will be immersed in the exciting, spontaneous and multifaceted world of improvised theater. On the stage of the new Theater im Zollhaus completely surprising stories and characters emerge from the moment. A unique and one-of-a-kind theater experience, created for one evening only.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/SPUNK_22</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/SPUNK_22</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
