<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Improv Festivals</title>
        <description>Improv Festivals - </description>
        <link>https://improfestivals.com</link>
        <link>https://improfestivals.com</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2022-12-10T16:35:36+00:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2022-12-10T16:35:36+00:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Improv Fest Ireland</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Ireland’s original international festival celebrating improvised theatre and comedy featuring workshops, shows, mixers and jams and probably the greatest improv after party in the world!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Improv_Fest_Ireland_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Sofia International Improv Fest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;6-th International Sofia Improv Fest&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us in celebrating improv! 
​
Masterful and fun teachers with lots of experience to learn from and hone your skills
Lots of performance opportunities on our beautiful theatrical stage
Fun afterparties at our dedicated improv club with a bar
One of the friendliest improv communities in Europe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An optional hiking day to the beautiful Vitosha mountain&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of that at an affordable travel destination with great food and fun people! Check us out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;www.shizi.bg/soimprovfest&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Sofia_International_Improv_Fest_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Samothrace Improv Retreat</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A summer Intensive Retreat&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Samothrace_Improv_Retreat_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-07-31T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Mount Olymprov</title>
                <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;welcome-to-mount-olymprov-festival&quot;&gt;Welcome to Mount Olymprov Festival&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a 3 year pause due to the pandemic, we are back, bigger and better than ever. With a lineup that will blow your mind, and activities that will make you fall in love with Greece, it is the obvious choice for next summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;with-a-stellar-lineup-of-11-instructors-and-16-different-shows-from-all-around-the-world&quot;&gt;With a stellar lineup of 11 instructors and 16 different shows from all around the world&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every year we make sure we bring you new talent to learn from, to enjoy mind-blowing improvised theater shows, to meet and socialize and live the full festival experience along 150+ improvisation enthusiasts from all corners of the planet.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Mount_Olymprov_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Mount_Olymprov_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Auckland Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;We have big news! We’re delighted to announce that international guest instructors Dan O’Connor, Patti Stiles Impro - official page and Andel Sudik will be joining us for the 2023 Auckland Improv Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The festival will take place in Auckland between April 11th and April 16th, 2023. During that week, we will have 10+ shows, 10+ workshops, masterclasses and social events for our participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hosted at the Covert Theatre in Ponsonby, the heart of Auckland City, the festival is directed by Matías Avaca and produced by Wade Jackson.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Auckland_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-04-11T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Edinburgh International Improv Festival</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Edinburgh International Improv Festival is held at the Scottish Storytelling Centre in Scotland’s beautiful capital city. It’s three days of workshops, shows and jams celebrating the best in improv from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this year’s festival we teamed up with World’s Greatest Improv School and had four of their teachers head across the pond to host workshops and perform.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Edinburgh_International_Improv_Festival_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Impro Amsterdam 2023</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;From the 25th of February to the 4th of March, IMPRO Amsterdam 2023 will rock Amsterdam Noord with eight days of high-quality international Improvisational Theatre. We have 29 shows from all over the world and 34 workshops that will teach you new skills or sharpen old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join us for a week and a day of the best Improv the international community has to offer and let’s make new friends from all over the world!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Impro_Amsterdam_2023_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-25T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Moth & Butterfly International Festival of Storytelling & Improvisation</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Moth &amp;amp; Butterfly International Festival of Storytelling &amp;amp; Improvisation is an Arts festival based in Galway in the West of Ireland. Our first festival was in 2021 and was presented digitally, in 2022 was hybrid with live events and the 2023 festival will be fully live from Galway, while retaining digital content for our international audiences. The festival will feature shows, workshops, arts events, story swaps, children’s events and bilingual presentations.  The festival highlights the artforms of improvisation and storytelling in all their presentations, and is particularly interested in the magical places where they intersect. The festival features local, national and international professional artists, as well as community participation. The festival is produced by Aoife Demel, with Artistic Director Órla Mc Govern, and core M &amp;amp; B crew members. Join our mailing list at www.mothandbutterflystories.com&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/Moth_&_Butterfly_International_Festival_of_Storytelling_&_Improvisation_23</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/Moth_&_Butterfly_International_Festival_of_Storytelling_&_Improvisation_23</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>SPUNK</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;theater anundpfirsich invites you to the 10th and last edition of SPUNK, the Zurich Improtheater Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From October 10 to 16, 2022, the festival ensemble shows with top-class guests from the USA, Great Britain, Poland, Germany, the Netherlands, Austria, Slovenia and Switzerland what improvised theater has to offer. The audience will be immersed in the exciting, spontaneous and multifaceted world of improvised theater. On the stage of the new Theater im Zollhaus completely surprising stories and characters emerge from the moment. A unique and one-of-a-kind theater experience, created for one evening only.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://improfestivals.com/SPUNK_22</link>
                <guid>https://improfestivals.com/SPUNK_22</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
