<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Improv Festivals</title>
        <description>Improv Festivals - </description>
        <link></link>
        <link></link>
        <lastBuildDate>2022-11-20T00:00:45+00:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2022-11-20T00:00:45+00:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>A</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;a&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>/a</link>
                <guid>/a</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-03-09T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>C</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;c&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>/c</link>
                <guid>/c</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>B</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;asdfsdf&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>/b</link>
                <guid>/b</guid>
                <pubDate>2023-02-01T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Spunk</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;theater anundpfirsich invites you to the 10th and last edition of SPUNK, the Zurich Improtheater Festival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From October 10 to 16, 2022, the festival ensemble shows with top-class guests from the USA, Great Britain, Poland, Germany, the Netherlands, Austria, Slovenia and Switzerland what improvised theater has to offer. The audience will be immersed in the exciting, spontaneous and multifaceted world of improvised theater. On the stage of the new Theater im Zollhaus completely surprising stories and characters emerge from the moment. A unique and one-of-a-kind theater experience, created for one evening only.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>/SPUNK</link>
                <guid>/SPUNK</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Musical Improv Weekend</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Baby Wants Candy (BWC) is thrilled to lead a two day music improv intensive in Switzerland. No musical improv experience needed.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on BWC’s signature form- a one hour, completely improvised musical with a full band, participants will learn how to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Create musical narratives while still maintaining the funny&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Use the game of the scene, characters, emotions &amp;amp; wants to create strong comedic songs&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Rhyme confidently and consistently&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Elevate your chorus’ to find the funny through dedicated word play training&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baby Wants Candy draws upon its years of experience, with over 4000 improvised musicals and counting, for its workshops. Our style combines what we consider are the best parts of UCB and io, both institutions at which we performed and taught for years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Space is limited so sign up early.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/baby_wants_candy</link>
                <guid>/baby_wants_candy</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-09-03T10:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Double feature</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;In this very special double feature, we present two unique improv shows in one fantastic night.
&lt;!--more--&gt;
First, Don’t Touch My Mushroom Improv will play their new improvised format “The Gathering” for the first time ever. It’s a show about a dramatic, life changing event, gathering friends and enemies, envious colleagues and backstabbing family, secret lovers and open haters. What happens at this event is a mystery to all of us. But we will find out together in “The Gathering”! With the musical support of Klearjos Papanicolaou.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But wait there’s more! The Basic Pitches, the one and only musical improv group of Zurich, will then take the stage and will perform a fully improvised musical with all its extravaganza: Singing, dancing, drama and comedy! This is their third show ever and after two grandiose shows at Theater Ida, they are playing for the first time in the city at Jenseits! With the musical support of Izaskun.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/double_show</link>
                <guid>/double_show</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Show</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A whole musical being improvised in front of your eyes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever heard of Hamilton? What about Cats? Maybe Grease? Well, this is nothing like that.
We are going to develop a whole story from your suggestions. It will be full of emotions and epic songs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are Basic Pitches!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The money we collect from this show will be donated to &lt;a href=&quot;https://novaukraine.org/&quot;&gt;Nova Ukraine&lt;/a&gt;, a
nonprofit organization  providing humanitarian aid to Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/first_musical</link>
                <guid>/first_musical</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-05-13T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>C</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;asdf&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>/c</link>
                <guid>/c</guid>
                <pubDate>2002-02-02T00:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
